<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Buyer</string>
    <string name="author1">Wan</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_book_description">BookDescription</string>
    <string name="title1">Pride and Prejudice</string>
    <string name="description1">Pride and Prejudice by Jane Austen is a classic love story that explores the social lives of 18th century English citizens. The story follows the relationship between Elizabeth Bennet and Fitzwilliam Darcy, who must overcome their pride and prejudice to fall in love and marry. The story is set in 1811 and 1812, primarily in the counties of Hertfordshire and Derbyshire.</string>
    <string name="TKaM">To Kill a Mockingbird is a 1961 novel by Harper Lee. It is a coming-of-age story about Scout and Jem Finch, and their father Atticus, as he defends a Black man falsely accused of rape. The novel explores themes of prejudice, integrity, justice, innocence, and good versus evil.</string>
    <string name="TGG">The Great Gatsby, novel by American author F. Scott Fitzgerald, published in 1925. It tells the story of Jay Gatsby, a self-made millionaire, and his pursuit of Daisy Buchanan, a wealthy young woman whom he loved in his youth. Set in 1920s New York, the book is narrated by Nick Carraway.</string>
    <string name="LoTR">The Lord of the Rings is a high fantasy novel by J.R.R. Tolkien that is considered the ultimate fantasy book. It is set in the fictional world of Middle-earth and follows the story of the War of the Ring, which centers on the magical One Ring. The book was originally intended as a sequel to The Hobbit (1937), but the story developed into an epic that takes place about 60 years after the events of that book.</string>
    <string name="Don">Don Quixote is a Spanish novel by Miguel de Cervantes, published in the early 1600s. The book is about a middle-aged nobleman who becomes obsessed with chivalry and sets out on adventures as a \"knight errant\". The story is told through the eyes of the book\'s narrator, Cide Hamete Benegali.</string>
    <string name="oneHs">Set in the fictional town of Macondo, the narrative follows seven generations of the Buendía family, weaving a rich tapestry of love, power, isolation, and destiny. From the town\'s inception to its foreordained demise, the tale encapsulates the cyclical nature of history and the universality of human experiences.</string>
    <string name="AliceW">Alice\'s Adventures in Wonderland is a 1865 book by Lewis Carroll about a girl who falls down a rabbit hole into a fantasy world. The story is a carnival-like reflection of Victorian society, and it lampoons the era\'s moralistic and hypocritical nature. The book is considered a classic children\'s book, but it\'s also popular with adults. \n</string>
</resources>